http://www.give.org/about-us/terms-of-use

For Donors
For Charities
For Media
Find a BBB
ABOUT US (current)
Get basic facts about BBB Wise Giving Alliance's mission,
activities, governance and finances.
Our Mission
Helping you give wisely, helping charities build trust.
FAQ
Get answers to the who, what, where, why and when of BBB Wise
Giving Alliance.
Board and Staff
Who serves on the staff and governing body of BBB Wise Giving
Alliance?
Financial
Access our Annual Report, IRS Form 990, and Audited Financial
Statements.
Privacy Policy
Read about our privacy policy to help maintain your trust and
protect your personal information.
Contact Us
How do you contact BBB Wise Giving Alliance?
GIVE WISELY
Learn about wise giving, issues addressed by BBB Charity
Standards, and how BBB Wise Giving Alliance completes evaluative
reports on charities.
Alphabetical List of Charities
Access the A-Z list of reports on nationality-soliciting
charities.
Our Accreditation Process
How does BBB Wise Giving Alliance produce evaluative reports
on charities?
BBB Standards for Charity Accountability
What are the BBB Standards for Charity Accountability?
20 standards addressing 4 themes: Governance, Results
Reports, Finances, and Truthful and Transparent
Representations.
Wise Giving Guide
Read the cover stories on charity subjects appearing in Wise
Giving Guide magazine.
Guidance and Tips
Find out about basic tips to help you make informed giving
decisions.
Contact Us
How do you contact BBB Wise Giving Alliance?
TOOLS AND RESOURCES
Access evaluative reports that show if a charity meets the BBB
Charity Standards. Order a free copy of Wise Giving Guide
magazine.
Alphabetical List of Charities
Access the A-Z list of reports on nationality-soliciting
charities.
Wise Giving Guide
Read the cover stories on charity subjects appearing in Wise
Giving Guide magazine.
National Charity Seal Holders List
Do you know which nationally-soliciting charities are licensed
to use the BBB Accredited Charity Seal?
Local Charity Review
Identify Better Business Bureaus that produce reports on
regionally-soliciting charities.
Give.org Donor Trust Report
Learn about our annual survey on the state of public trust in
the charitable sector.
Inquire or File a Complaint About a Charity
Can’t find a report about a charity? Or, want to file a
complaint about a charity?
ScamTracker
Have you been the subject of a potential charity scam? Report
it here.
TAKE ACTION
Ask for a charity to be evaluated by BBB Wise Giving Alliance.
File a complaint about a charity. Report suspicious activity on
ScamTracker.
Sign Up for the BBB's Give.org Newsletter for Donors
Get a weekly newsletter that shares the latest on items of
interest to donors.
Inquire or File a Complaint About a Charity
Can't find a report about a charity? Or, want to file a
complaint about a charity?
ScamTracker
Have you been the subject of a potential charity scam? Report
it here.
Request Stickers Supporting BBB's Give.org
Ask for labels that announce you verify charity
trustworthiness by visiting Give.org
Refer Us to a Friend
Recommend a friend that wants to learn how to make wise giving
decisions.
Request a Wise Giving Guide
Ask for a free copy of the Wise Giving Guide magazine.
NEWS & UPDATES
Read the Wise Giving Wednesday blog each week to keep up to date
on charity issues.
Read Our Latest News
Access the latest Wise Giving Wednesday blog - to help inform
you about charity giving issues.
View Our Video Library
View video interviews of charity executives and videos about
other wise giving subjects.
ABOUT US
About Us
Get basic facts about BBB Wise Giving Alliance's mission,
activities, governance and finances.
FAQ's
Our Mission
Helping you give wisely, helping charities build
trust.
FAQ
Get answers to the who, what, where, why and when of
BBB Wise Giving Alliance.
Board and Staff
Who serves on the staff and governing body of BBB Wise
Giving Alliance?
Financial
Access our Annual Report, IRS Form 990, and Audited
Financial Statements..
Privacy Policy
Read about our privacy policy to help maintain your
trust and protect your personal information.
Contact Us
How do you contact BBB Wise Giving Alliance?
GIVE WISELY
Give Wisely
Learn about wise giving, issues addressed by BBB Charity
Standards, and how BBB Wise Giving Alliance completes
evaluative reports on charities.
FAQ's
Alphabetical List of Charities
Access the A-Z list of reports on
nationality-soliciting charities.
Our Accreditation Process
How does BBB Wise Giving Alliance produce evaluative
reports on charities?
BBB Standards for Charity Accountability
What are the BBB Standards for Charity Accountability?
20 standards addressing 4 themes: Governance, Results
Reports, Finances, and Truthful and Transparent
Representations.
Wise Giving Guide
Read the cover stories on charity subjects appearing
in Wise Giving Guide magazine.
Guidance and Tips
Find out about basic tips to help you make informed
giving decisions.
TOOLS & RESOURCES
Tools and Resources
Access evaluative reports that show if a charity meets the
BBB Charity Standards. Order a free copy of Wise Giving
Guide magazine.
FAQ's
Alphabetical List of Charities
Access the A-Z list of reports on
nationality-soliciting charities.
Wise Giving Guide
Read cover stories on charity subjects appearing in
Wise Giving Guide magazine.
National Charity Seal Holders List
Do you know which nationally-soliciting charities are
licensed to use the BBB Accredited Charity Seal?
Local Charity Review
Identify Better Business Bureaus that produce reports
on regionally-soliciting charities.
Give.org Donor Trust Report
Learn about our annual survey on the state of public
trust in the charitable sector.
Inquire or File a Complaint About a Charity
Can’t find a report about a charity? Or, want to
file a complaint about a charity?
ScamTracker
Have you been the subject of a potential charity scam?
Report it here.
The Heart of Giving Podcast
The Heart of Giving Podcast features stories and conversations focused on the power that giving has on the human spirit and our society as a whole.
TAKE ACTION
Take Action
Ask for a charity to be evaluated by BBB Wise Giving
Alliance. File a complaint about a charity. Report
suspicious activity on ScamTracker.
FAQ's
Sign Up for the BBB's Give.org Newsletter for
Donors
Get a weekly newsletter that shares the latest on
items of interest to donors.
Inquire or File a Complaint About a Charity
Can't find a report about a charity? Or, want to file
a complaint about a charity?
ScamTracker
Have you been the subject of a potential charity scam?
Report it here.
Recommend a friend that wants to learn how to make
wise giving decisions.
Request a Wise Giving Guide
Ask for a free copy of the Wise Giving Guide magazine.
NEWS & UPDATES
News and Updates
Read the Wise Giving Wednesday blog each week to keep up
to date on charity issues.
FAQ's
Read Our Latest News
Access the latest Wise Giving Wednesday blog - to help
inform you about charity giving issues.
View Our Video Library
View video interviews of charity executives and videos
about other wise giving subjects.
Contact Us
Terms of Use  Hyperlinking:1. The following organizations may link to our website without prior written approval:Government agencies;Search engines;News organizations;Online directory distributors when they list us in the directory may link to our website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the websites of other listed businesses; andSystemwide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our website.Accredited Charities licensed to use the BBB Accredited Charity Seal.These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products
or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party's site.2. We may consider and approve in our sole discretion other link requests from the following types of organizations:Commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources such as Chambers of Commerce, American Automobile Association, AARP and Consumers Union;Dot.com community sites;Associations or other groups representing charities, including charity giving sites,Online directory distributors;Internet portals;Accounting, law and consulting firms whose primary clients are businesses; andEducational institutions and trade associations.We will approve link requests from these organizations if we determine that: (a) the link would not reflect unfavorably on us or our accredited charities (for example, suspect charitable solicitations, such as those that falsely claim charitable tax-exempt
status, shall not be allowed to link); (b) the organization does not have an unsatisfactory record with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility associated with the hyperlink outweighs the absence of BBB accreditation; and (d) where the link
is in the context of general resource information or is otherwise consistent with editorial content in a newsletter or similar product furthering the mission of the organization.These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and it products
or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party's site.If you are among the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to www.give.org, you must notify us by sending an e-mail to info@give.org.
Please include your name, your organization name, contact information (such as a phone number and/or e-mail address) as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our website, and a list of the URL(s) on
our site to which you would like to link. Allow 2-3 weeks for a response.Approved organizations may hyperlink to our website as follows:By use of our corporate name; orBy use of the uniform resource locator (web address) being linked to; orBy use of any other description of our website or material being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party's site.No use of BBB's torch logo or other design trademark of IABBB will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement from IABBB. Use of IABBB design marks specific to a particular BBB program (such as the accredited business advertising
program or the accredited charity seal program), participants and businesses should consult with their respective area BBBs for proper trademark usage, advertising guidelines and restrictions.Your Content:There are places on our site where your comments or other information you provide to BBB may be made available to the public. As noted in our submission rules, we expect that you will honor the intellectual property rights of others in your submission.
Copyright owners or agents that believe submissions are violative of their rights may provide BBB notice of this as set forth in Paragraph 9 of our submission rules.Framing:Without prior approval and express written permission, you may not create frames around our webpages or use other techniques that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our website.Content Liability:We shall have no responsibility or liability for any content appearing on your website. You agree to indemnify and defend us against all claims arising out of or based upon your website. No link(s) may appear on any page on your website or within
any context containing content or materials that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.Reservation of Rights:We reserve the right at any time and in our sole discretion to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our website. You agree to immediately remove all links to our website upon such request. We also reserve the right to amend
these terms and conditions and its linking policy at any time. By continuing to link to our website, you agree to be bound to and abide by these linking terms and conditions.What You Should Know About Links We Have On Our Website:From time to time, we may, with permission from the site owner, decide to link to websites that we determine may be of interest to our visitors. These websites may offer educational, governmental or other resources or may be owned or controlled by
other third parties.We are not responsible for the content of any linked site, any link(s) contained in any linked site, or any changes or updates to the information contained in such sites. We provide links to third party sites only as a convenience and the inclusion
of any such link on our site does not imply our endorsement of either the site, the organization operating such site, or any products or services of that organization. A visit to any site or page from our website via any such link is done entirely
at your own risk.We strongly recommend reading any Standard Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Disclaimers or other notifications that may be found on any such third party websites. Under no circumstances will we be held responsible or liable, directly or indirectly,
for any loss or damage that is caused or alleged to have been caused in connection with the use of, or reliance on, any content, goods or services available on any other site.If you find any link on our website or any linked website objectionable for any reason, you may contact us about this at info@give.org. We will consider requests to remove links but will have
no obligation to do so or to respond directly to you.
